thelott.com 2017-11-08

# Privacy Policy - Tatts Group

Tatts Group’s vision is to be the world’s best gambling group and part of this vision means taking a robust attitude when it comes to handling the personal information in our possession.  This privacy policy sets out how we handle personal information in accordance with the Australian Privacy Principles ( **APPs** ) and is applicable to Tatts Group Limited (ACN 108 686 040) and all of its subsidiaries that conduct business within Australia. In this policy, a reference to Tatts Group is a reference to Tatts Group Limited and all of its subsidiaries.

  1. **Collecting Personal Information  
**We interact with many customers, partners and members of the community on a daily basis and we collect personal information during those interactions.We may collect personal information including your name, contact details, residential address, date of birth, geographic location as well as details of your interactions with us. The type of information that we collect will vary depending on whether you are opening an account, participating in a loyalty program, entering a promotion, self-excluding, applying for employment or to become an agent or engaging with us as a contractor or service provider.We will ordinarily provide you with an explanation as to why we are collecting your personal information at the time that we collect it. Sometimes, we are required by law to collect your personal information, for example, to comply with our obligations under the _Anti-Money Laundering and Counter-Terrorism Financing Act 2006_ (Cth) we need to engage in a customer identification and verification process and to comply with some of our responsible gambling commitments we may need to engage in oversight of your gambling activities with us.While there are some circumstances where it will be possible for you to interact with us on an anonymous basis or using a pseudonym, these are rare and we will generally need to know who you are in order to comply with our legal obligations and to assist you.
  2. **Use and Disclosure of Personal Information  
**We will use your personal information for the purposes for which it was collected and also for related purposes.For example, if you provide your personal information to us in order to open an account we may use your information in order to contact you and provide you with information about our products and services or to enter you in additional promotions. We may also engage in predictive monitoring activities in relation to our responsible gambling commitments or utilise records of your interactions with us for audit, market research or training purposes.We do not generally disclose personal information to third parties except: 
    1. where third party contractors appointed by us require access to personal information held by us to perform services for us or on your behalf;
    2. where we reasonably believe it is necessary to protect any person and/or our rights or property;
    3. where we are required or authorised by law to do so;
    4. to recognised governing bodies responsible for the administration of events on which our businesses conduct wagering where there are reasonable grounds to suspect that – there has been a breach of the rules of the event, rules of the governing body or a threat to the probity of the event on which we conduct wagering; or
    5. with your consent.
  3. **Tatts Group Websites  
**Our websites may collect “click stream” information (such as areas of our websites you have accessed and the time and date of access) from your use of our websites. We may also collect Doubleclick Adserving information (such as whether a marketing campaign has been effective) from your use of our websites.  
We may also store “cookie” information, such as user preferences relating to the use of our websites. A cookie is a small data file that may be placed on the computer of a web user (usually in the browser software folder). The information collected may be used to offer our products and services directly to you and customise and improve websites. If you do not want us to store cookie information on your computer, you can set your browser to disable this feature. This may mean you will not be able to take full advantage of the services offered on our websites.
  4. **Security of Personal Information  
**Tatts Group will take reasonable steps to (a) protect the personal information it holds from misuse and loss and from unauthorised access, modification or disclosure; and (b) to ensure that the personal information that it collects, uses or discloses is accurate, complete and up to date. Some of your personal information may be stored on cloud based solutions some of which may have servers based in countries such as the United Kingdom, Japan and the United States of America.
  5. **Updating and Seeking Access to Personal Information  
**If you have reason to believe personal information which we hold about you is inaccurate, out of date, incomplete, irrelevant or misleading please contact the relevant Tatts Group company and specify the information you wish to change, noting that some Tatts Group companies are subject to laws which require us to collect certain information about you. We rely on you providing us with up to date personal information.  You are also welcome to request access to personal information Tatts Group holds about you however in some circumstances a charge will apply to us retrieving your information. There are certain situations where we may decline to give you access to your personal information however if we deny access we will provide you with the reason.
  6. **Changes to the Privacy Policy  
**Tatts Group reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time and to notify you by posting an updated version of the policy on our website, [www.tattsgroup.com](http://www.tattsgroup.com/).
  7. **Resolving your privacy concerns  
**If you have any issues that you wish to raise with us or you wish to make a complaint regarding our management of your personal information please contact us. We take complaints about privacy concerns seriously and we will work to resolve your complaint and correct any errors on our part. 

Our contact details are as follows:  
****Tatts Group Limited****

Street Address:  
87 Ipswich Road,  
Woolloongabba QLD 4102

Postal Address:  
Locked Bag 7 Coorparoo DC, QLD 4151

Phone Number:  

Email:
